[
  {
    "currentgame": [
      {
        "_id": "a1",
        "currentQuestion": "Who is Sachin Tendulkar?",
        "options": ["Doctor",
          "Cricketer",
          "Engineer",
          "Lawyer"
        ],
        "correctOption": "Cricketer",
        "currentScore": 0,
        "cue": "Vishant"
      },

      {
        "_id": "a2",
        "currentQuestion": "Start spreading the news, I’m leaving today” are the opening lines of which song?",
        "options": [  "Latch",
          "Closer",
          "All The Way Up",
          "I Want You"
    ],
        "correctOption": "Closer",
        "currentScore": 0,
        "cue": "Vishant"
      },

      {
        "_id": "a3",
        "currentQuestion": "In which television programme was I don’t believe it a catchphrase?",
          "options": [  "Friends",
          "Quantico",
          "Seinfield",
          "House Of Cards"
    ],
        "correctOption": "House Of Cards",
        "currentScore": 0,
        "cue": "Vishant"
      },

      {
        "_id": "a4",
        "currentQuestion": "You Give Love a Bad Name and Livin’ on a Prayer were early hits for which band?",
       "options": [   "The Beatles",
          "Rolling Stones",
          "Pilot",
          "U2"
    ],
        "correctOption": "The Beatles",
        "currentScore": 0,
        "cue": "Vishant"
      },


      {
        "_id": "a5",
        "currentQuestion": "What was the surname of Del Boy and Rodney in Only Fools and Horses?",
        "options": ["Stifler",
          "Adams",
          "Gomez",
          "Hendricks"
    ],
        "correctOption": "Stifler",
        "currentScore": 0,
        "cue": "Vishant"
      },

      {
        "_id": "a6",
        "currentQuestion": "In which year was a cinematic Space Odyssey set?",
        "options": [    "2012",
          "2013",
          "2014",
          "2015"
    ],
        "correctOption": "2012",
        "currentScore": 0,
        "cue": "Vishant"
      },

      {
        "_id": "a7",
        "currentQuestion": "Who was the lead singer of T. Rex?",
        "options": [    "Bob James",
          "Peter",
          "Chris",
          "Jack"
    ],
        "correctOption": "Bob James",
        "currentScore": 0,
        "cue": "Vishant"
      },

      {
        "_id": "a8",
        "currentQuestion": "Which silent movie actor created “The Little Tramp” character?",
        "options": [    "Charlie Chaplin",
          "Peter",
          "Jason",
          "Chris"
    ],
        "correctOption": "Charlie Chaplin",
        "currentScore": 0,
        "cue": "Vishant"
      },

      {
        "_id": "a9",
        "currentQuestion": "In which film does the line “Toto, I’ve a feeling we’re not in Kansas anymore” appear?",
        "options": [     "Crew",
          "Heat",
          "Office",
          "Hemlet"
    ],
        "correctOption": "Crew",
        "currentScore": 0,
        "cue": "Vishant"
      },

      {
        "_id": "a10",
        "currentQuestion": "Who plays Lewis in Morse and its spin-off, Lewis?",
        "options": ["Him",
          "Not You",
          "That Guy",
          "No One"
    ],
        "correctOption": "Not You",
        "currentScore": 0,
        "cue": "Vishant"
      },

      {
        "_id": "a11",
        "currentQuestion": "What is Indiana Jones’s profession?",
        "options": ["Archaeologist",
          "Doctor",
          "Engineer",
          "Lawyer"
    ],
        "correctOption": "Archaeologist",
        "currentScore": 0,
        "cue": "Vishant"
      },

      {
        "_id": "a12",
        "currentQuestion": "Which policeman was at the centre of the Pink Panther movies?",
        "options": ["Travis",
          "Keith",
          "Chris",
          "Joey"
    ],
        "correctOption": "Travis",
        "currentScore": 0,
        "cue": "Vishant"
      },

      {
        "_id": "a13",
        "currentQuestion": "Which musical instruments are also called Kettledrums?",
        "options": ["Keyboard",
          "Guitar",
          "Turn-Table",
          "Drums"
    ],
        "correctOption": "Turn-Table",
        "currentScore": 0,
        "cue": "Vishant"
      },
      {
        "_id": "a14",
        "currentQuestion": "Some Enchanted Evening, Happy Talk and There is Nothing Like a Dame are songs from which musical?",
        "options": ["Some Love",
          "Kickstart",
          "The Woman",
          "Can't Stay"
    ],
        "correctOption": "Some Love",
        "currentScore": 0,
        "cue": "Vishant"
      },

      {
        "_id": "a15",
        "currentQuestion": "Which long-running Australian series is set in Summer Bay?",
        "options": ["Victoria Bash",
          "Melbourne Bash",
          "Sydney Bash",
          "Canberra Bash"
    ],
        "correctOption": "Victoria Bash",
        "currentScore": 0,
        "cue": "Vishant"
      },

      {
        "_id": "a16",
        "currentQuestion": "In which film does a farmer played by Kevin Costner build a baseball diamond in his cornfield?",
        "options": ["Moneyball",
          "Brookeback Mountain",
          "Taken",
          "Push"
    ],
        "correctOption": "Moneyball",
        "currentScore": 0,
        "cue": "Vishant"
      },

      {
        "_id": "a17",
        "currentQuestion": "Fox Mulder and Dana Scully were the main characters in which television series?",
        "options": ["NCIS",
          "The Wanted",
          "Kids",
          "Players"
    ],
        "correctOption": "NCIS",
        "currentScore": 0,
        "cue": "Vishant"
      },

      {
        "_id": "a18",
        "currentQuestion": "Which former schoolteacher from Neath has become a big-selling singer?",
        "options": ["Blake Shelton",
          "Chris Rock",
          "Kid Cudi",
          "Drake"
    ],
        "correctOption": "Blake Shelton",
        "currentScore": 0,
        "cue": "Vishant"
      },

      {
        "_id": "a19",
        "currentQuestion": "Who played Maximus Decimus Meridius in a 2000 Ridley Scott film?",
       "options": ["Meg Ryan",
          "Ridley",
          "Brad Pitt",
          "Chris Tucker"
    ],
        "correctOption": "Meg Ryan",
        "currentScore": 0,
        "cue": "Vishant"
      },

      {
        "_id": "a20",
        "currentQuestion": "How many red balloons did Nena take into the pop charts?",
        "options": ["6",
          "2",
          "12",
          "10"
    ],
        "correctOption": "6",
        "currentScore": 0,
        "cue": "Vishant"
      },

      {
        "_id": "a21",
        "currentQuestion": "Which of the Muppets did a stand-up comedy routine which tended not to be particularly good?",
        "options": ["Pup",
          "Cole",
          "Dylan",
          "Lewis"
    ],
        "correctOption": "Pup",
        "currentScore": 0,
        "cue": "Vishant"
      },

      {
        "_id": "a22",
        "currentQuestion": "In what sort of music might you hear scat singing?",
        "options": ["Reggae",
          "Electronic",
          "Hip-Hop",
          "lawyer"
    ],
        "correctOption": "Reggae",
        "currentScore": 0,
        "cue": "Vishant"
      },

      {
        "_id": "a23",
        "currentQuestion": "Which television series is set in William McKinley High School, Lima, Ohio?",
        "options": ["Glee",
          "24",
          "The Vampire Diaries",
          "The Walking Dead"
    ],
        "correctOption": "Glee",
        "currentScore": 0,
        "cue": "Vishant"
      },

      {
        "_id": "a24",
        "currentQuestion": "With which band did Pete Doherty come to fame?",
        "options": ["Daughtry",
          "One Republic",
          "Papa Roach",
          "Linkin Park"
    ],
        "correctOption": "Daughtry",
        "currentScore": 0,
        "cue": "Vishant"
      },

      {
        "_id": "a25",
        "currentQuestion": "Which soap opera started in 1972, and lost a word from its title in 1989?",
        "options": ["Seinfield",
          "The Comedy Show",
          "The Office",
          "The Wire"
    ],
        "correctOption": "Seinfield",
        "currentScore": 0,
        "cue": "Vishant"
      },

      {
        "_id": "a26",
        "currentQuestion": "What started with Sergeant in 1958 and ended with Columbus in 1992?",
        "correctOption": "Engineer",
"options": ["Doctor",
          "Cricketer",
          "Engineer",
          "lawyer"
    ],
        "correctOption": "Engineer",
        "currentScore": 0,
        "cue": "Vishant"
      },

      {
        "_id": "a27",
        "currentQuestion": "What is the name of the character played by Michael Douglas in the Wall Street films?",
        "options": ["Charlie",
          "Douglas",
          "Dirk",
          "Kirk"
    ],
        "correctOption": "Charlie",
        "currentScore": 0,
        "cue": "Vishant"
      },

      {
        "_id": "a28",
        "currentQuestion": "From which opera does the March of the Toreadors come?",
        "options": ["Singin In The Rain",
          "Black Swan",
          "The Graduate",
          "The Bachelor"
    ],
        "correctOption": "Singin In The Rain",
        "currentScore": 0,
        "cue": "Vishant"
      },

      {
        "_id": "a29",
        "currentQuestion": "Who played the Vicar of Dibley?",
        "options": ["Christian",
          "Duncan",
          "Drake",
          "Steve"
    ],
        "correctOption": "Christian",
        "currentScore": 0,
        "cue": "Vishant"
      },

      {
        "_id": "a30",
        "currentQuestion": "What are the surnames of the title characters in Romeo and Juliet?",
        "options": ["Saint",
          "D'Souza",
          "Douglas",
          "Jones"
    ],
        "correctOption": "Saint",
        "currentScore": 0,
        "cue": "Vishant"
      },
    ]
  }
]
